[{"answer": "The bottom line.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "By the way, why are you in so much debt?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "It sounded bad and it all sounded I hate to say very naive.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Whatever came afterwards, whatever context he was trying to put it in, it sounded bad, didn't it?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "I think many bankers have got away with it, but I think many of the executives on wall street have got away with it as well which is why the CFP, the consumer financial protection bureau that President Obama put into place.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Do you think they have gotten away with it in many ways?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Do you think America is now coming out of the recession?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "I mean, to me, it's very worrying.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "So, why get them back?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "It's serious but it's been serious.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "This is serious stuff, isn't it?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, the country as a business isn't running like a good business.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "The country as a business?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "I think they do need to go back to building things.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Do you think, as many do, that America needs to go back to building things rather than consuming?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "It's the way because it got so expensive to hire a laborer here with the insurance, with everything, we couldn't afford it.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Why is it the way?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "But, in their way, they are.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "They should be looking after their own country, shouldn't they?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "It would make me feel awful.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "When you graduate college, if you had 20, 30, $40,000 as student loan debt, how would that make you feel?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "He should go to the college that gives him 100 percent scholarship.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Suze, what do you do then?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "They would.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Suze, the problem is not specific comparison, people will get a better education at a private school right now than they would from a non-thief main school in America, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "That's a good answer.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Got it people?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "They are nervous about that kind of commitment because they don't have 20 percent down.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What kind of advice would you give them?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "That's gone for now.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "That's gone, isn't it?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Isn't that a better way of looking at this?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "That has change, isn't it?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Are you ready for it?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "It's not more of a priority, but --", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "Did you just say helping your siblings with a wedding is more of a priority for you over getting out of credit card debt or saving money for your own retirement?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Do I have to say?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "If I average everything out, it's probably around like 15 percent.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "At what interest rate?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Shopping.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What were they doing?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "There's a saying that I have, when you feel less than, you spend more than.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "It's like you have to be personally responsible, haven't you?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Yes, there will be one thing I change about the card.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Given all the attacks that have come on you, is there anything you will change about the card?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Well, I was trying, deny, deny, deny.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "What were you thinking?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I think we should be saluting him.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "We should be saluting him, shouldn't we?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Hi Piers.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Natalie?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "RMAN: You live in New York City.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "What is our problem?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "Almost everything.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "What are things that most people are wasteful about, do you think?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Well, I personally would tell you weddings.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What are the most common ways people waste money?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "-- too much of my life.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "Isn't it worse to do that than stay at home and make love with each other?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "I want to rally the troops, you see.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "But do you feel at times like your spirit is broken, because nobody is listening to you?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "About 3,000?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "That was really good.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Oh, how did I know that?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I was afraid you were going to ask me that.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Now, so how much credit card dent do you have?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "About that.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "Fifteen, 20?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "This is now getting very, very unusual.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Did I impress you again?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "You know, I have had so many.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "If I could relive a moment for you, what would it be?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "The luckiest thing that has ever happened to me, the greatest thing that has happened to me is KT.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "So that's the greatest thing.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "Because all the money in the world, actually, if you don't have love in your life, is pointless, isn't it?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "One.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "The other signature question of mine, of course, is how many times, Suze, have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "Romney.", "docId": "120201pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "GOP pick?", "qSentId": 760}]